

DATA DIRI

Date and Place of Birth

Jakarta, March 31st 2008

Gender

Male

Status

Single

Nationality

Indonesia

CONTACT

- +62 82111557981
- michaelsatrian@gmail.com
- Jl. BBD III Blok B1 no. 105, Mekarsari, Cimanggis, Depok, 16452

SOCIAL MEDIA

@m_satriach31

https://mic3103.github.io/port ofolio-michael/

ABOUT ME

A web developer with 2 years of experience specializing in frontend development. My 6 years of experience in video editing allows me to bring a unique perspective and contribute effectively to web development projects that demand a strong visual understanding.

EDUCATION

SMA MARSUDIRINI BOGOR 2023-NOW

SMP MARSUDIRINI BOGOR 2020-2023

SD PERMATA BUNDA CIMANGGIS 2014-2020

EXPERIENCES

OSIS SMP MARSUDIRINI BOGOR

Multimedia Division (2021-2022)

OSIS SMA MARSUDIRINI BOGOR

ICT Development Division (2023-2024)

Coding & Web Design

 Achieved 2nd Place in the Web Design Competition at KBOF 2024

Video Editing

- Achieved 2nd Place in the Short Movie Competition at M-Fest:UROZION 2019
- Video Editor & Multimedia at Marsudirini Bogor Dormitory

SKILLS

- Proficient in programming languages HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, PHP, and JavaScript.
- Skilled in Video Editing & Visual Effects using Filmora and Adobe After Effects.